<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Best of Breda</string>
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="menu_nav_sights">Sights</string>
    <string name="menu_nav_routes">Routes</string>
    <string name="menu_nav_help">Help</string>
    <string name="menu_nav_termsofservice">Terms of Service</string>
    <string name="menu_toolbar_search">Search</string>
    <string name="helpactivity_header_instructions">Instructions</string>
    <string name="termsofactivity_header">TERMS AND CONDITIONS FOR USE, REPRODUCTION AND DISTRIBUTION</string>
    <string name="termsofactivity_text">Terms of Service example</string>

    <string name="GPS_off">Your GPS function is not turned on</string>

    <string name="NotificationChannel_name">Nearby sight</string>
    <string name="NotificationChannel_Description">The notification appears when a user is near a sight with the tour running</string>

    <string name="HelpText">After opening het app you will get to see the map of Breda. When you select the
        icon with the three horizontal stripes, you will get to see a menu. In this menu you have a choice between
        the possible routes that you can walk.
    \nAfter you have chosen one of these routes, you can walk them. If you select the menu icon while walking the
        tour, you will find a list of the sight that are along the route. When you select on of these sights, you
        can view the detailed information, pictures and videos. It is also possible to view this information by
        selecting one of the sight-markers.
    \nAs you walk, the part of the route that you have walked will be visibly marked. When you come within the 25
        meter zone of a sight, you will receive a notification informing you that you are near a sight. if you tap
        on the notification, you can vies the information of this sight.
    \nIf you stray form the tour, the app will give the directions to return to the tour.</string>
</resources>